Now that we've trained the model,
我们已经训练了模型
we can load the weights that got the best validation accuracy.
我们可以加载达到最佳验证准确率的权重了
When we try out the model on the images in the testing set,
当我们用测试集中的图片实验模型时
we see that the model gets over 98% accuracy.
我们看到模型的准确率超过了 98%
That's not bad, and MLPs are a nice solution here.
结果不错 这里 MLP 是个很好的解决方案
Other solutions towards the MNIST classification task and
对于其他关于 MNIST 分类任务的解决方案和测试集误差
their errors on the test dataset can be explored at the link provided below.
请访问下面的链接
You'll find that the best algorithms,
你会发现最佳算法
or the ones with the least test error,
或者测试误差最小的算法
are the approaches that make use of convolutional neural networks.
是利用卷积神经网络的方法
We note that more typically,
我们注意到
in many problem domains,
在很多问题领域
CNNs and MLPs do not yield comparable results.
CNN 和 MLP 并不能产生理想的结果
The MNIST database is special in that it's very clean and preprocessed.
MNIST 数据集比较特殊 数据很干净并且已经预处理过
All images of digits have roughly the same size and
所有数字图片都差不多大
are centered in a 28-by-28-pixel grid.
并在 28x28 像素网格中居中
You can imagine that if instead of having to
想象下 不再是分类
classify the digit within these very clean images,
这些非常整洁的数字图片
if you had to work with images where the digit could appear anywhere
相反 对于要处理的图片 数字可能位于任何位置
within the image and sometimes appear quite small or quite large,
并且数字有时候很小 有时候很大
it would be a much harder task.
这样的话 任务会难很多
In the case of real-world messy image data,
对于现实生活中的杂乱图片数据
CNNs will truly shine over MLPs.
CNN 的确比 MLP 好了很多
For some intuition for why this might be the case,
为何在某些情况下是这种情形
we saw that in order to feed an image to an MLP,
那是因为我们发现为了向 MLP 提供图片
you must first convert the image to a vector.
必须首先将图片转换为向量
The MLP then treats the converted image as
MLP 然后将转换后的图片
a simple vector of numbers with no special structure.
处理为简单的数字向量 没有特殊结构
It has no knowledge of the fact that these numbers were
它不知道这些图片本来是
originally spatially arranged in a grid.
位于网格中
CNNs, in contrast, are built for the exact purpose
相反 CNN 专门用于处理
of working with or elucidating the patterns in multidimensional data.
或发现多维数据中的规律
Unlike MLPs, CNNs understand the fact that image pixels that are
与 MLP 不同 CNN 知道
closer in proximity to each other are more
相互靠近的图片像素
heavily related than pixels that are far apart.
比离得很远的像素关系更紧密
But MLPs and CNNs do share some important similarities.
但是 MLP 和 CNN 的确有一些共同点
For instance, just as multilayer perceptron models are composed of a stack of layers,
例如 就像多层感知器模型由一堆层级组成的一样
so are convolutional neural networks.
卷积神经网络也是这样
We also won't need to introduce any new lost functions and
并且我们不需要引入任何新的损失函数
you'll still use the same optimizers to minimize your chosen loss function.
依然使用相同的优化程序来最小化所选的损失函数
CNNs do differ from MLPs in the types of hidden layers that can be included in the model.
CNN 与 MLP 的差别是模型可以包含的隐藏层类型
Over the next several videos,
在接下来的几个视频中
we'll present these different types of layers and provide
我们将介绍这些不同类型的层级
some intuition about their roles in the deep network.
并形象地说明它们在深度网络中的作用